The OneGuide hub and app give you shortcuts to movies and TV.
If you’ve browsed in any of the categories in OneGuide recently,
you’ll see the OneGuide app in the Most Recently Used list.
Right from here you can jump straight to watching TV,
browsing the TV listings, or browsing all your video apps together.
When you start the OneGuide app, it opens to last category you browsed.
You can quickly switch to another by pressing
the Menu button on your controller and choosing one from the menu.
The menu also gives you quick access to TV listings, trending, and favorites.
To get a quick overview of lots of shows at once,
go to OneGuide on Home.
At the top is featured content from video apps that you can jump into,
and if you have TV configured you’ll see the top trending shows right here.
Below that are the categories for browsing, and the movies and TV
you’ve purchased for your own collection.
Continue on down to see selections from across your video apps,
so you don’t have to start each app individually to find something to watch.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.